export const cssQuiz = {
  quiz_name: "CSS Attributes",
  quiz_id: 10004,
  quiz_category: "css",
  questions: [
    {
      questionId: 1,
      question: "What does the 'color' property do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Sets the background color",
        B: "Sets the text color",
        C: "Sets the border color",
        D: "Sets the font size",
      },
      correctAnswer: "B",
    },
    {
      questionId: 2,
      question: "What does the 'background-color' property do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Sets the background color",
        B: "Sets the text color",
        C: "Sets the border color",
        D: "Sets the font size",
      },
      correctAnswer: "A",
    },
    {
      questionId: 3,
      question: "What does the 'margin' property do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Applies spacing between text lines within an element",
        B: "Sets the space between the content and the padding of an element",
        C: "Defines the space inside the element, between its content and border",
        D: "Creates space around an element, outside of its border",
      },
      correctAnswer: "D",
    },
    {
      questionId: 4,
      question: "What does the 'padding' property do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Creates space inside an element, between its content and border",
        B: "Sets the distance between elements",
        C: "Adjusts the size of an element's border",
        D: "Changes the spacing between lines of text",
      },
      correctAnswer: "A",
    },
    {
      questionId: 5,
      question: "What does the 'font-size' property do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Sets the width of the characters in a text",
        B: "Specifies the size of the font used in an element",
        C: "Sets the spacing between characters in a text",
        D: "Defines the thickness of the text",
      },
      correctAnswer: "B",
    },
    {
      questionId: 6,
      question: "What does the 'border' property do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Sets the border length",
        B: "Sets the border orientation",
        C: "Defines the width, style, and color of an element's border",
        D: "Sets the roundness of the border",
      },
      correctAnswer: "C",
    },
    {
      questionId: 7,
      question: "What does the 'display' property do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Changes the position of an element on the page",
        B: "Sets whether an element is treated as a block or inline box and the layout used for its children",
        C: "Sets the spacing between elements",
        D: "Adjusts the size of an element",
      },
      correctAnswer: "B",
    },
    {
      questionId: 8,
      question: "What does the 'position' property do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Controls the alignment of an element on the page (left, center, right)",
        B: "Defines how an element is positioned on the page (static, relative, absolute, fixed, sticky)",
        C: "Specifies the coordinates of an element relative to its container",
        D: "Determines the flow of text around an element",
      },
      correctAnswer: "B",
    },
    {
      questionId: 9,
      question: "What does the 'overflow' property do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Sets how an element is aligned within its container",
        B: "Defines how much space should be between elements",
        C: "Controls the padding inside an element",
        D: "Specifies how to handle content that's larger than an element's box",
      },
      correctAnswer: "D",
    },
    {
      questionId: 10,
      question: "What does the 'text-align' property do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Specifies the horizontal alignment of text within an element",
        B: "Sets the vertical alignment of text within an element",
        C: "Controls the spacing between lines of text",
        D: "Adjusts the size of the text within an element",
      },
      correctAnswer: "A",
    },
  ],
};
